Political Research Associates Records MS014
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Subject files, 1949 -- 2010; MS014.003; 78.0 Cubic Feet
  - North American Congress on Latin America (NACLA), circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004157; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - North American Man Boy Love Association, 1990; MS014.004158; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina Against Racist and Religious Violence, circa 1985 -- 1990; MS014.004159; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Northeast Indiana Rescue, circa 1993 -- 1994; MS014.004160; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - The Norwegian National League of Minnesota, 1995; MS014.004161; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Notre Dame Institute, circa 1994 -- 1995; MS014.004162; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Novak, Michael, circa 1982 -- 1985; MS014.004163; 2 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 7-8)
  - N.S. publications, circa 1983; MS014.004164; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Freeze, Anti-, circa 1981 -- 1986; MS014.004165; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Numbers USA, circa 2001; MS014.004166; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - O'Connor, Sandra Day, circa 1981 -- 1989; MS014.004167; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - O'Toole, Martin K., circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004168; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Oak Park Freedom Committee, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004169; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Obando y Bravo, Miguel, circa 1987; MS014.004170; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Occult, circa 2001; MS014.004171; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - OC International, circa 198 -- 1991; MS014.004172; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Occupational Safety, 1981; MS014.004173; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - October Surprise, circa 1981 -- 1988; MS014.004174; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Odinism, circa 1987; MS014.004175; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - OEF International/Overseas Education Fund, circa 1986 -- 1987; MS014.004176; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Of the People, circa 1999; MS014.004177; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Office of the Chief Counsel, circa 2000; MS014.004178; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Office of Management and Budget, circa 1983 -- 1988; MS014.004179; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Of the People, circa 1994 -- 1996; MS014.004180; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Oklahoma City Bombing 1995, circa 1995; MS014.004181; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Oklahomans for Children and Families, circa 1997; MS014.004182; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Olasky, Marvin, circa 2001; MS014.004183; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Old Nazis Response, circa 1988; MS014.004184; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Olson, Carl, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004185; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Olin, Foundation, circa 1983 -- 1992; MS014.004186; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - OMB Watch, circa 1995; MS014.004187; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Omega Group, Inc., circa 1988; MS014.004188; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Omega 7, circa 1982; MS014.004189; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - On Principle calendar of events, circa 1983 -- 1984; MS014.004190; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - On Wings of Eagle, circa 1998 -- 2003; MS014.004191; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - One Nation, circa 2002; MS014.004192; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Open Doors with Brother Andrew, circa 1989 -- 2003; MS014.004193; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Operation California Inc., circa 1986 -- 1990; MS014.004194; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Operation Rescue, circa 1990 -- 1998; MS014.004195; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Operation Rescue California, circa 1993 -- 1995; MS014.004196; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Operation Rescue West, circa 1997; MS014.004197; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Operation Save America, circa 2000; MS014.004198; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Opportunity International, circa 1991; MS014.004199; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - Opus Dei, circa 1983; MS014.004200; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - Orbis, circa 1988 -- 1992; MS014.004201; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Order, The, circa 1985 -- 1988; MS014.004202; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 47)
  - Oregon, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004203; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - Organizing, circa 1995 -- 2003; MS014.004204; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 49)
  - Other losses, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004205; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 50)
  - Our Father's House, 1991; MS014.004206; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 51)
  - Outpost, circa 1996 -- 1997; MS014.004207; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 52)
  - Overseas Press Service, circa 1987; MS014.004208; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 53)
  - Owen, Robert, circa 1983 -- 1990; MS014.004209; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 54)
  - Public Institute for Public Policy Research, circa 1984 -- 1986; MS014.004210; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 55)
  - Pacific Legal Foundation, circa 1990; MS014.004211; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 56)
  - Paladin Press, circa 1994; MS014.004212; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 57)
  - P-2, circa 1987; MS014.004213; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 58)
  - Palou (Luis) Evangelistic Association, circa 1979 -- 1994; MS014.004214; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 59)
  - Palestinian / Israeli Affairs, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004215; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 60)
  - Pamyat, circa 1988; MS014.004216; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 61)
  - Pan American Development Foundation SEC, circa 1983 -- 1994; MS014.004217; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 62)
  - Paralife/ Para Vida, circa 1987 -- 1998; MS014.004218; 1 Folder(s) (Box 57, Folder 63)
  - Paramilitary groups, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004219; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Paras, George E., 1982; MS014.004220; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Parents and Friends of Ex-Gays, circa 1996 -- 1999; MS014.004221; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Parents' Music Resource Center, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004222; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Parents' Right Coalition, circa 2002; MS014.004223; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Parents Television Council, circa 2002 -- 2003; MS014.004224; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Parker, J. A., circa 1971 -- 1991; MS014.004225; 2 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 7-8)
  - Star Parker, circa 1998; MS014.004226; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Parnet, circa 1992 -- 1993; MS014.004227; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Partners of the Americas / Companeros de las Americas, circa 1983 -- 1990; MS014.004228; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Pasztor, Laszlo, circa 1989 -- 2003; MS014.004229; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Pasztor - notes, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004230; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Pataki, George, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004231; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - The Pathfinder, circa 1989 -- 1994; MS014.004232; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - The Pathfinder Fund, circa 1987 -- 1990; MS014.004233; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Patriot Movement, circa 2003; MS014.004234; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Patriot Movement, Hamilton Standoff, circa 1990; MS014.004235; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Patriot's Defense Foundation, circa 1991; MS014.004236; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Patterson, Edward, circa 1983 -- 1984; MS014.004237; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Paul, Ron, circa 1983 -- 2007; MS014.004238; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - The Paulist Press, 1995; MS014.004239; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Programa de Ayuda para los Vecinos del Altiplano, circa 1983 -- 1986; MS014.004240; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Pawlick, Edward, circa 1999; MS014.004241; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Pearson Foundation (Robert), circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004242; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Pearson, Roger, circa 1982 -- 1984; MS014.004243; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Peltzman, Sam, circa 1981; MS014.004244; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Pendleton, Clarence, circa 1981 -- 1988; MS014.004245; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Peninsula of Harvard, Inc., circa 1995 -- 1996; MS014.004246; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - People Against Racist Terror, circa 1993 -- 1994; MS014.004247; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - People Against Taxation, 1992; MS014.004248; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - People for the American Way, circa 1993 -- 2001; MS014.004249; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - People for the American Way, circa 1981 -- 2002; MS014.004250; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - People of Life, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004251; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Percy, Chuck, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004252; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Perloff, James, circa 1988; MS014.004253; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Perot, Ross, circa 1977 -- 1992; MS014.004254; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Peters, Pete, circa 1989 -- 1992; MS014.004255; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Peru, circa 1987 -- 1991; MS014.004256; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Pew Foundation, circa 1989 -- 1992; MS014.004257; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Phelps, Rev. Fred Sr., circa 1994 -- 2000; MS014.004258; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Philip, James, circa 1983; MS014.004259; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Philippines, circa 1986 -- 1990; MS014.004260; 2 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 43-44)
  - Philippines / Anticommunism, circa 1985 -- 1989; MS014.004261; 1 Folder(s) (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Asia Pacific Anti Communist League, circa 1987; MS014.004262; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Philippines / Repression, circa 1988; MS014.004263; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Phillips, Kevin, circa 1982 -- 1990; MS014.004264; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Phillips, Howard, circa 1983 -- 1982; MS014.004265; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Phillips, Thomas L., circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004266; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Phillips Publishing, circa 1982; MS014.004267; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Phoenix Group, 1983; MS014.004268; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Phoenix Institute Project, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004269; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Pierce, Samuel R., circa 1982 -- 1983; MS014.004270; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Pierce, William, circa 1995 -- 2000; MS014.004271; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Pilgrim Family Institute, 1994; MS014.004272; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Pillon, Juliana Geron, circa 1982; MS014.004273; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Pines, Burton Yale, circa 1989; MS014.004274; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Pink Sheet on the Left, circa 1993; MS014.004275; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Pioneer Fund, circa 1989 -- 2001; MS014.004276; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Job postings - mailings, circa 1996 -- 2004; MS014.004277; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Pioneer Brand Report, circa 1987 -- 2003; MS014.004278; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Pipes, Richard, 1991; MS014.004279; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Planned Parenthood, circa 1992 -- 2003; MS014.004280; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Planning, programming, budget, evaluation system, circa 1982; MS014.004281; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Plattner, Marc F, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004282; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Plymouth Rock Foundation, circa 1994; MS014.004283; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, circa 1979 -- 1982; MS014.004284; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, 1987; MS014.004285; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Poindexter, Vice Admiral John, 1987; MS014.004286; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Police misconduct, circa 1981 -- 1996; MS014.004287; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Policy Review, circa 1992 -- 2000; MS014.004288; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Polish Catholic Convent controversy, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004289; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Polish Freedom Fighters, circa 1986 -- 1991; MS014.004290; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Political Action Committee, circa 1981 -- 1988; MS014.004291; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Political backlash, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004292; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Political correctness, circa 1982 -- 1995; MS014.004293; 5 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 32-36)
  - Political Dynamite, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004294; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Political Ecology Group, circa 1997 -- 2000; MS014.004295; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Political Economy Research Center, circa 1999 -- 2001; MS014.004296; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Polls, circa 1984; MS014.004297; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Popes, pretenders, circa 2002; MS014.004298; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Population Communications, circa 2003; MS014.004299; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - The Population Council, circa 1988 -- 1990; MS014.004300; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Population-Environment Balance, circa 1999 -- 2007; MS014.004301; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Population Renewal Office, circa 1993; MS014.004302; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - Population Research Institute, circa 1999; MS014.004303; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Pop stop, circa 2001; MS014.004304; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - Populism, circa 1984 -- 1995; MS014.004305; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - The Populist Forum, circa 1970 -- 1999; MS014.004306; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Pornography, circa 1986 -- 1987; MS014.004307; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - Posey, Tim, 1986; MS014.004308; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Posner, Richard, circa 1984 -- 1986; MS014.004309; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 52)
  - Power of Prophecy, circa 1970 -- 1990; MS014.004310; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 53)
  - PRA attacks - incite, circa 1993; MS014.004311; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 54)
  - PRA attacks white supremacist, circa 1986; MS014.004312; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 55)
  - PRA attacks - NCLC, circa 1980 -- 1993; MS014.004313; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 56)
  - PRA attacks - Dan Brendt, circa 1990 -- 1993; MS014.004314; 1 Folder(s) (Box 59, Folder 57)
  - Posse Comitatus, 1975 -- 1984; MS014.004315; 18 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 1-17)
  - PRA presentations, 1992; MS014.004316; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Post Abortion Ministries, circa 1980s; MS014.004317; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Post Against Times, 1984; MS014.004318; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Post Eagle, 1990; MS014.004319; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Powell, Colin, 2001; MS014.004320; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Prairie Fire, 1988; MS014.004321; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - TP Precious Metals, 1996; MS014.004322; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Priests for Life, 2000; MS014.004323; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Presbyterian Church in America, 1986 -- 1991; MS014.004324; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Presbyterians for Democracy and Religious Freedom, 1988; MS014.004325; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Presidential Task Force on Adoption, 1987; MS014.004326; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Presidents Report - Citizens for Excellence in Education, 1993 -- 1996; MS014.004327; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Presiding Bishop's Fund for World Relief, 1990; MS014.004328; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Press, 1985; MS014.004329; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Priests for Life, 2004 -- 2009; MS014.004330; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Pre-Trib Perspectives, 1995 -- 2004; MS014.004331; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - The Priestly Fraternity of Peter, 2003; MS014.004332; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Prison Fellowship Ministries, 1991 -- 2008; MS014.004333; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Privacy, 1991; MS014.004334; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Private Aid, 1984 -- 1987; MS014.004335; 3 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 37-39)
  - PACT/Private Agencies Collaborating Together, 1986; MS014.004336; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Private Voluntary Organizations: Gender Analysis, 1982 -- 1986; MS014.004337; 2 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 41-42)
  - Privatization, 1992 -- 2002; MS014.004338; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - Problem Pregnancy of Worcester, 1994 -- 1998; MS014.004339; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 44)
  - The Pro-Choice Report, 1993; MS014.004340; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - Pro Choice Resource Center, 1993; MS014.004341; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 46)
  - ProEnglish, 2003 -- 2009; MS014.004342; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 47)
  - Pro-Family, 1982 -- 1985; MS014.004343; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 48)
  - Pro-Family Coalition at UN, 2000; MS014.004344; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 49)
  - Pro-Family Forum, 1990; MS014.004345; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 50)
  - Pro Family Legislative Network, circa 1990s; MS014.004346; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 51)
  - Pro-Family Resource Center, 2002; MS014.004347; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 52)
  - Professors World Peace Academy, 1992; MS014.004348; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 53)
  - Progress and Freedom Foundation, 1998 -- 1999; MS014.004349; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 54)
  - Project Censored, 1997 -- 2008; MS014.004350; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 55)
  - Project Democracy, 1984; MS014.004351; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 56)
  - Project Hope, 1989; MS014.004352; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 57)
  - Project Paperclip, circa 1990s; MS014.004353; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 58)
  - Project Reality, 1999 -- 2002; MS014.004354; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 59)
  - Project Respect, circa 1980s; MS014.004355; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 60)
  - Project Tocsin, 1993 -- 1995; MS014.004356; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 61)
  - Project USA, 2001; MS014.004357; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 62)
  - Pro-Life Action League, 1984 -- 1994; MS014.004358; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 63)
  - Pro-Life Action Ministries, 1994 -- 1998; MS014.004359; 1 Folder(s) (Box 60, Folder 64)
  - Pro-Life Alliance of Gays and Lesbians, 1993 -- 1998; MS014.004360; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Prometheus Books, 1997 -- 1998; MS014.004361; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Promise Keepers - Secondary Sources (TP), 1993 -- 1997; MS014.004362; 6 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 3-8)
  - Property Rights Foundation of America, 1998; MS014.004363; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Prophetic Vision, 1994; MS014.004364; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Protect America's Children, 1976; MS014.004365; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Protocols of the Elders of Zion, circa 1980s; MS014.004366; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Prouty, Fletcher, 1990 -- 1993; MS014.004367; 2 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 13-14)
  - PTL Club/Jim Baker, 1987 -- 1989; MS014.004368; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Public Advocate, 1999 -- 2000; MS014.004369; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Public Affairs Research Institute of New Jersey, 1999; MS014.004370; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Public Broadcasting, Attacks On, 1992; MS014.004371; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Public education, 1997 -- 1998; MS014.004372; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Public Defending, 1998 -- 2000; MS014.004373; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Public Enemy, 1989; MS014.004374; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - The Public Interest, circa 1990s; MS014.004375; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Public opinion, 1987; MS014.004376; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Public Policy Education Fund, circa 1980s; MS014.004377; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Public relations firms, 1987 -- 1991; MS014.004378; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Public Service Research Council, 1992; MS014.004379; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - The Public Voice, 1986; MS014.004380; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Pullen, Penny, circa 1980s; MS014.004381; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Pure Love Alliance, 1997; MS014.004382; 1 Folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Pure Love Alliance, 1997; MS014.004383; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - PVOs - Mother Jones-Key Clips, 1982; MS014.004384; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Quality Education Inc., circa 1970s; MS014.004385; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Quayle, Dan, 1988 -- 1993; MS014.004386; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Quest, 1982 -- 1983; MS014.004387; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Margaret Quigley, 1993; MS014.004388; 2 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 6-7)
  - Quincentennial, 1990 -- 1991; MS014.004389; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Race and religious right, 1993; MS014.004390; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Race hate/Brockton, 1994; MS014.004391; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Racism/Asian, 1983 -- 1988; MS014.004392; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Racism (TP), circa 1990s; MS014.004393; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Racism in South Boston, circa 1990s; MS014.004394; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Racially motivated violence, 1988 -- 1990; MS014.004395; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Radical Right - the term, 1994; MS014.004396; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Radio - Right Wing Topic, 1987; MS014.004397; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Radio for Peace International, 1996; MS014.004398; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Radio Free America, 1988 -- 1990; MS014.004399; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Ralph Myles Publishers, Inc., 1979 -- 1983; MS014.004400; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Rambo Coalition (Restore a More Benevolent World Order), 1987; MS014.004401; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Ranch Rescue, 2000; MS014.004402; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Rand, Ayn, 1982; MS014.004403; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Rand, Howard B., 1995; MS014.004404; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - A. Phillip Randolph Inst., 1987 -- 1989; MS014.004405; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Rappaport, Jim, 1990; MS014.004406; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Ratzinger, Joseph Cardinal, 1984 -- 1987; MS014.004407; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Raymond, Walt, 1988; MS014.004408; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Read, Otis B. Jr., circa 1980s; MS014.004409; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Reader's Digest, 1983; MS014.004410; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Reagan administration, circa 1980s; MS014.004411; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Reagan, Ronald, circa 1980s; MS014.004412; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Reagan Youth Founding, 1985; MS014.004413; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Reaper, The, 1978; MS014.004414; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Reason, circa 1990s; MS014.004415; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Reason Foundation, circa 1990s; MS014.004416; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Recursive Rasoning Research Ctr., 1993 -- 1995; MS014.004417; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Redeem Our Country (ROC), circa 1980s; MS014.004418; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Red Alert Ministry, 1989; MS014.004419; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Refugee Relief International, 1984 -- 1987; MS014.004420; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Ralph Reed, 1997; MS014.004421; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Reed, Thomas, 1983 -- 1985; MS014.004422; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Referenda and initiatives, 1984; MS014.004423; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Refuse and Resist, 2001; MS014.004424; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - Regent University, 1990 -- 2003; MS014.004425; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Regeneration, 2001 -- 2009; MS014.004426; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Regeneration Books, 1987 -- 1989; MS014.004427; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Regenery Publishing Inc., 1995; MS014.004428; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Regulation/Deregulation, 1987 -- 1988; MS014.004429; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Rehnquist, William H., 1986; MS014.004430; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Reilly, Hugh L., circa 1980s; MS014.004431; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Judith Reisman, 1984; MS014.004432; 1 Folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 51)